A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Program Staff Files FA537
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Program Staff Files
1972-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA537
2.62 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Arranged in 2 series:
1. EPP Chronological Correspondence.
2. Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs.
Scope and Contents
Primarily contains correspondence and committee records.
- EPP Chronological Correspondence, 1977-1978; I
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1977 October 31-1978 January 27 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1978 January 30-March 31 (Box 1)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1978 April 3-June 2 (Box 1)
- Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1972-1980; II
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1972 April-December (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1975 January-June (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1975 July-December (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs, 1976 January-May (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Pension Inequality Report and Background, 1974-1980 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Original Pension Memorandum, 1976 July 28 (Box 2)
  - Coordinating Committee on Women's Programs -- Revised Pension Memorandum, 1977 April 22 (Box 2)